Vladimir Lenin or Joseph Stalin was from
Владимир Ленин или Иосиф Сталин был из
this
этого
family Hello about you 18 years old there is Zdra and
рода Здравствуйте о вам 18 лет есть Здра
what kind of ensign is on the wall Well
есть а ну что за прапор на стене Ну а
what do you think I don’t know maybe either
что как вы думаете не знаю может або
Imperial or
Имперский або
Ukrainian Well what do you think I don’t
украинский Ну вот а вы какой думаете не
know you are scrolls Now a second Wait
знаю ты свитки Сейчас секунду Подождите
you see me no no now I’m not for you in
ты видишь меня нет нет сейчас я не вам в
a second and you you Streamer Yes Streamer Yes
секунду а вы вы Стример Да Стример Да
Streamer Well, that’s good That’s good And you’re
Стример Ну это хорошо Это хорошо А вы
not swearing here Well, you just see me the
здесь не ругаетесь Ну просто меня видите
Imperial flag I’m telling you, I’m telling you
флаг Имперский Я же говорю я же говорю
Imperial, you see, I understand you wo
Имперский видите я же понимаю ругаться
n’t swear with  I’m not interested, then
не будете со мной не мне интересно то
Turn on the light, I’ll talk to the man with the imperial
Включите Свет я с человеком с имперским
flag, I’m interested, Why talk to
флагом поговорю мне интересно А зачем со
me? Speak And shine it on you, it’s
мной Говорите А посвети там же вас
written We are Russians, God is with us, yes Well,
написано Мы русские с нами бог да А ну
dedicate it, yes Show me exactly that’s it, yes
посвятите да Покажите ещё именно вот вот
We are Russians with you, yes  And when, for
вот да Во Мы русские с вами да А когда
example, I know it was the flag of the
вот например я знаю это был флаг
Romanov emperors,
императоров Романовых
yes, who were the Romanovs, can
да да кто такие Романовы были не
you tell me they were rulers, it would be a
подскажете это были правители это бы
rich family, in my opinion, and didn’t teach me about the
семья богатая по-моему и не учил меня со
society, more or less not rich, like from
общество более-менее не богатая типа из
this family, there were a lot of
этого рода ти было очень много
rulers I understand  But
правителей Поня А вот
let's vladimi Joseph Stalin was from
Давайте владими Иосиф Сталин был из
this
этого
family the last last ruler from
рода последний последним правителем из
this from the Romanov family Who was you
этого из рода Романова Кто был ругаться
can't swear yes yes Well, okay I won't Well, in
же нельзя да да Ну хорошо не буду Ну
my opinion Lenin I don't know Lenin Yes I understand, well,
по-моему Ленин не знаю Ленин Да понял ну
he's Vladimir Ilyich Lenin Yes, this is
он же Владимир Ильич Ленин Да это ж
Lenin -  this is his nickname, like a party one
Ленин - это его кличка типа партийная
And so he was Vladimir
так А так он был Владимир
Romanov from Ulyanovsk Yes, they knew it or
Романов из Ульяновска Да это знали или
guessed it And this is not obvious because
угадали А это Не ну очевидно потому что
Well, clearly not Stalin that
Ну явно не Сталин что
he is a question Yes well done, I know correctly
он вопрос Да молодец правильно знаю А
Why look like this Why Lenin
почему смотри давай так Почему э Ленин
was the last of the Romanov family  Why
был последним из рода Романовых почему
didn’t he deprive the heirs after
он не лишил наследников после
himself? I don’t know. I’m telling history, I don’t teach. I don’t
себя я не знаю я говорю историю не учу я
teach such facts. Well, look, you hung it. That’s the
смотри ты ж ты ж повесил Вот это это это
flag. Yes, that was hanging in Lenin’s office.
флаг Да который у Ленина в кабинете
Yes, when Stalin came, he wanted to hang it like that.
висел Да когда пришёл Сталин он захо так
Yes, that’s it, I just
повешать е да вот ли Просто я так
wanted it that way, I liked it I hung it
захотел мне понравилось Я повесил его
when Stalin came to power Yes, when he
Сталин пришёл когда к власти Да когда он
poisoned Lenin Yes, he changed it when they
отравил Ленина Да вот он э поменял когда
started when they started people re just
начали когда начали людей ре просто
When Stalin came Yes, he changed the
Когда Сталин пришёл Да он он поменял
flag to red and everything he said would be blood
флаг на красный и всё сказал будет кровь
like yes And Lenin He had this
типа да А Ленин Вот у него был вот этот
imperial flag like yes and there he had it
имперский флаг типа да и там у него
by the way E I don’t remember at first Lenin
кстати Э я не помню э сначала у Ленина
didn’t write this We are Russians God is with us
не писалось вот это Мы русские с нами
so and then in my opinion he in
бог так а потом по-моему он в
1920 yes by resolution of the
1920 году да постановлением
party congress  Bolsheviks
съезда партии большевиков
[laughter]
[смех]
[music]
[музыка]
yes The main thing is to put on the imperial flag yes We
да Главное нацепить имперский флаг да Мы
Russians are with us like God is like yes then
русские с нами бог типа да
Lenin was left from the
то Ленин был остани из
Romanovs
Романовых
shi na y telr right now ovin and
ши на й telr прям зараз овин а
so much more and more respectfully
пок дуже и дуже важливо